unifiedremote.com 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy – Unified Remote

This Privacy Policy describes the policies and procedures of Unified Intents AB (“Unified Intents”, “we”, “our” or “us”) on the collection, use and disclosure of your information on [www.unifiedremote.com](http://www.unifiedremote.com/) (the “Site”) and the services, features, content or applications we offer (collectively with the Site, the “Services”). We may receive information about you from various sources, including: (i) if you register for the Site and the Services, through a user account on the Services (your “Account”); (ii) your use of the Services generally; and (iii) from third party websites and services. When you use the Services, you are consenting to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

## What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

This Privacy Policy covers the treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) gathered when you are using or accessing the Services. This Privacy Policy also covers our treatment of any Personal Information that our business partners share with us or that we share with our business partners.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited to any third party websites, services and applications (“Third Party Services”) that you may access through the Services or to individuals that we do not manage or employ. We cannot take responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those Third Party Services. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of any Third Party Services you access.

## What Information Do We Collect?

The information we gather enables us to personalize, improve and continue to operate the Services. In connection with certain aspects of the Services, we may request, collect and/or display some of your Personal Information. We may collect the following types of information from our users.

### IP Address Information and Other Information Collected Automatically:

We may automatically receive and record information from your web browser when you interact with the Services, including your IP address and cookie information. This information is used for fighting spam/malware and also to facilitate collection of data concerning your interaction with the Services (e.g., what links you have clicked on).

Generally, the Services may automatically collect usage information, such as the number and frequency of visitors to the Site. We may use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, but not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us and third parties authorized by us to figure out how often individuals use parts of the Services so that we can analyze and improve them.

### Email Communications:

Unified Intents may send occasional promotional materials through email if you have signed up to our newsletter or explicitly provided your email address to us. You will have the option to opt-out of these emails by responding directly inside of the email itself.

### Information Collected Using Cookies:

Unified Intents stores cookies for visitors to the Site in order to identify them for relevant advertising through third party websites, also known as retargeting. Unified Intents also gathers anonymous usage information from our visitors via cookies for usage with Google Analytics.

Cookies are pieces of text that may be provided to your computer through your web browser when you access a website. Your browser stores cookies in a manner associated with each website you visit. We may use cookies to enable our servers to recognize your web browser and tell us how and when you visit the Site and otherwise use the Services through the Internet.

Our cookies do not, by themselves, contain Personal Information, and we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other Personal Information to tell us who you are. As noted, however, we may use cookies to identify that your web browser has accessed aspects of the Services and may associate that information with your Account if you have one.

Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways.

This Privacy Policy covers our use of cookies only and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties. We do not control when or how third parties place cookies on your computer. For example, third party websites to which a link points may set cookies on your computer.

To support and enhance the Services, we may serve advertisements, and also allow third parties advertisements, through the Services. These advertisements are sometimes targeted and served to particular users and may come from third party companies called “ad networks.” Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms.

Unified Intents partners with third party advertising networks to display advertisements targeted to visitors of the Services. To do so, Unified Intents stores a cookie for visitors for the purpose of displaying advertising also commonly known as retargeting. The data that is stored and collected is non-identifiable and anonymous.

Unified Intents does not disclose any Personal Information to any third party companies for purposes of partnerships or advertising.

### Aggregate Information:

We may collect statistical information about how both unregistered and registered users, collectively, use the Services (“Aggregate Information”). Some of this information may be derived from Personal Information. This statistical information is not Personal Information and cannot be tied back to you, your Account or your web browser.

We do not share any information that we collect to any third party.

## Is Information About Me Secure?

We are committed to protecting your collected Personal Information. To do so we employ a variety of industry-standard security technologies and measures to help protect all of our information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure.

## What Choices Do I Have Regarding My Information?

You can opt-out of anonymous data collection on our website. See Google Analytics' [currently available opt-outs](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

You can opt-out of anonymous data collection in the mobile application by disabling it in the preferences of the app.

## What If I Have Questions or Concerns?

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy using the Services, please contact us.
